<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SeedApp</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="notifiche">Notification</string>
    <string name="suono">Sound</string>
    <string name="lingua">Language</string>
    <string name="sicurezza">Security</string>
    <string name="privacytitolo">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="PrivacyTesto">This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use and protect your personal information within our application (hereinafter “l\\\'App”).         By using the App, you agree to the terms of this policy.          Data collected During the use of the App, we collect various types of personal data to facilitate the user experience and optimize the services offered: Personally identifiable information: name, email address, phone number (only when provided voluntarily). Geolocation data: precise or approximate location of the user, used to improve features such as localized suggestions or notifications. Application usage data: how, when and what features are used, to personalize and optimize the content and services offered. Sensitive data: any personal data that the user voluntarily shares with the App that could be considered sensitive, such as health data or personal preferences.     Data Usage The data collected is used exclusively to improve the use and functionality of the l\\\'App. Specifically:  To personalize content and provide personalized suggestions. To provide smooth navigation and better interaction with the features of the App.   Translated with DeepL.com (free version) To analyze the use of the App and improve the quality of our services. To send notifications, alerts or updates, based on user preferences. 3. Data Sharing. We do not share your personal data with third parties unless we are required to do so:  To fulfill legal obligations: in case of legal obligations or requests from competent authorities. With third-party service providers: for services necessary for the App (e.g., hosting services or data analysis), and only if those parties provide equivalent data protections. 4. Data Protection. We take appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect your data from unauthorized access, loss, alteration, or disclosure.  5. User Rights. You have the right to access, rectify or delete your personal data and to restrict or object to its processing. To exercise these rights, you can contact us at the email address “SeedApp@gmail.com”.  6. Updates We reserve the right to update this privacy policy periodically. Any changes will be communicated through l\\\'App or other appropriate means.  Contact If you have any questions or concerns about this Policy, please contact us at \\e-mail “SeedApp@gmail.com”.  Translated with DeepL.com (free version)To analyze the use of the App and improve the quality of our services. To send notifications, alerts or updates, based on user preferences. 3. Data Sharing. We do not share your personal data with third parties unless we are required to do so:  To fulfill legal obligations: in case of legal obligations or requests from competent authorities. With third-party service providers: for services necessary for the App (e.g., hosting services or data analysis), and only if those parties provide equivalent data protections. 4. Data Protection. We take appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect your data from unauthorized access, loss, alteration, or disclosure.  5. User Rights. You have the right to access, rectify or delete your personal data and to restrict or object to its processing. To exercise these rights, you can contact us at the email address “SeedApp@gmail.com”.  6. Updates We reserve the right to update this privacy policy periodically. Any changes will be communicated through l\\\'App or other appropriate means.  Contact If you have any questions or concerns about this Policy, please contact us at \\e-mail “SeedApp@gmail.com”.  Translated with DeepL.com (free version)</string>
    <string name="ita">italian</string>
    <string name="eng">English</string>

    <string name="Vibration">Vibration</string>
    <string name="obbiettivi">Target Notifications</string>
    <string name="sostenib">Sustainability Notifications</string>
    <string name="meteo">Weather Notifications</string>
</resources>